[
  {
    "question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Dirk%20the%20Daring",
    "answers": [
      "Dirk%20the%20Daring",
      "Arthur",
      "Sir%20Toby%20Belch",
      "Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"
    ]
  },
  {

    "question": "What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Homo%20Sapiens",
    "answers": [
      "Homo%20Ergaster",
      "Homo%20Sapiens",
      "Homo%20Erectus",
      "Homo%20Neanderthalensis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Bilius",
    "answers": ["Arthur", "John","Bilius","Dominic"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Robert%20Kirkman",
    "answers": [
      "Stan%20Lee",
      "Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson",
      "Robert%20Kirkman",
      "Bilius"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Electric%20Company",
    "answers": ["Electric%20Company","Water%20Works", "Chance", "Community%20Chest"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Kingston",
    "answers": ["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Kingston","Dar%20es%20Salaam", "Kano"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20",
    "correct_answer": "1962",
    "answers": ["1492", "1963","1962","1987"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "answers": ["True","False"]
  },
  {

    "question": "In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F",
    "correct_answer": "%2412.7%20Billion",
    "answers": [
      "%2495%20Million",
      "%24956%20Million",
      "%2412.7%20Billion",
      "%242.7%20Billion"
    ]
  },
  {

    "question": "How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
    "correct_answer": "55",
    "answers": ["50", "60", "54","55"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Alonsus%20Faol",
    "answers": [
      "Uther%20the%20Lightbringer",
      "Alonsus%20Faol",
      "Alexandros%20Mograine",
      "Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "answers": ["False", "True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Coils",
    "answers": ["Wires","Coils","Collectors", "Tesla"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Vanilla",
    "answers": ["Peach", "Strawberry", "Vanilla","Mint"]
  },
  {
    "question": "These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.",
    "correct_answer": "Poland%20and%20Lithuania",
    "answers": [
      "Hutu%20and%20Rwanda",
      "North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea",
      "Poland%20and%20Lithuania",
      "Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F",
    "correct_answer": "George%20Clooney",
    "answers": [
      "Matthew%20Perry",
      "Dennis%20Miller",
      "Pierce%20Brosnan",
      "George%20Clooney"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Plastic%20Beach",
    "answers": ["Demon%20Days", "Humanz", "The%20Fall"]
  },
  {

    "question": "Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {

    "question": "In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F",
    "correct_answer": "No%20Mercy",
    "answers": [
      "No%20Mercy",
      "Subway%20Sprint",
      "Hospital%20Havoc",
      "Blood%20Harvest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Hong%20Kong",
    "answers": ["India","Hong%20Kong","Australia", "Ireland"]
  }
]
